goldenstatemint.com 2019-04-25

# Our Privacy Policy at Golden State Mint LLC

Home | Golden State Mint Privacy Policy

|   
---|---  
  
## Privacy Policy

Golden State Mint (GSM) is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect any and all personal information that you provide online or directly via email or telephone. GSM does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information regarding its customers to any third party.

### GSM's Commitment to Online Security

Procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of any and all personal information provided to Golden State Mint online, which is deemed by GSM to be personal/ confidential in all instances. This information is never marketed, sold, or provided to any third-party.

### Personal Information that GSM May Collect Online and In Order Process

Golden State Mint collects the following types of personal information online and via emails & telephone calls made directly to GSM: names, mailing addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and specific product request information, as well as direct order placement. This information is voluntarily submitted online by website visitors to GSM via various Request Forms filled out online and submitted for follow-up by GSM. Any information collected from visitors to this website will only be used in serving our customers, in completing our business transactions with our customers, and not shared with third parties.

### How GSM May Use Personal Information Collected Online

As stated previously, GSM will not use your personal information other than for the purpose for which it was originally submitted and intended.  We use personal information strictly to provide information services, to reply to product/service inquiries, and for direct order placement and fulfillment. GSM maintains several mailing lists from which subscribers can be removed by merely replying to the relevant email with an “Unsubscribe” message in the subject line; all mailing lists are solely comprised of site visitor requested mailings.

### Rare Instances When Your Information May Be Shared

GSM will release personal information to appropriate governmental authorities only under the following circumstances:

  * Where release is required by law (for example, under subpoena) or regulation, or is requested by a government agency conducting investigations or proceedings
  * Where evidence indicates that an individual or company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of.

### Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate

If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information GSM may have on file, please email us with the new information or your review request at info@goldenstatemint.com

### Online Visitor Tracking

GSM websites are not set up to track, collect, or distribute personal information not entered by its visitors.  GSM site analysis logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to the sites. This information is used for internal purposes to provide better site accessibility and for marketing purposes, but the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 

### Questions/Concerns 

If you have a question or concern with regard to Golden State Mint’s compliance with this privacy policy or the policy as stated, you may contact us at [info@goldenstatemint.com](mailto:info@goldenstatemint.com) or call 800-320-8260.

### Subject to Applicable Laws and Regulations

This Privacy Policy is subject to applicable law and applicable regulations.
